

CONTACT

1 (226) 980-9134 Phone Number gsing994@gmail.com Email www.GurmanSingh.com Website

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (Hons) Concentration: Media, Information and Technology Marketing & Communication

The University of Western Ontario

SKILLS

PROCESS MANAGEMENT

SaaS & IaaS BASIC ARCHITECTURE

MARKETING STRATEGY

DIGITAL ADVERTISING

MOBILE MARKETING

WEBSITE DESIGN/HTML



Gurman Singh

Experienced Product Marketing Manager

SUMMARY

An accomplished Marketing Professional with over 4 years of Fortune 500 software marketing. Experience in strategy, advertising, social media, copywriting and press engagement, leading over 4 year-long campaigns to drive over 200 million downloads and 250 million monthly impressions. Highly organized, detail-oriented, and conscientious self-starter, able to strategize and prioritize effectively to accomplish multiple tasks with creativity, enthusiasm and humor.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) - Product Marketing Manager

July 2016 - Present

- Communicated Radeon Software's value proposition, messaging and competitive positioning to target customers
- Created PRDs and worked with product management teams to define and deliver product enhancements
- Collaborated closely with internal teams to develop channel marketing programs, demos and launch events
- Conducted campaign analyses to develop company-wide KPIs which anticipate industry trends and provide recommendations for product features, promotional channels, customers, and new technologies
- Created marketing content for sales enablement, marketing newsletter and other customer viewable web content



The University of Western Ontario - Microsoft Specialist

Jan 2015 - May 2016

- Worked with licensing and CRM software to sell SaaS
- Evaluated the software needs of faculty and businesses to increase efficiency
- Provided products which promoted the integration of accessibility with technology
- Worked directly with sales agents and used various negotiation and sales techniques



Intercept Group - Marketing Lead and Retail Specialist - Microsoft Technology Sept 2014 - May 2016

- Managed a cross-functional team to target various markets with targeted individual campaigns
- Stimulated Microsoft product sales by creating and launching promotions for Software as a Service (SaaS) products
- Led social media marketing campaigns on Facebook and Twitter to increase brand awareness and purchase intent
- Conducted market research to gain valuable customer behavior preferences to better serve customers
- Created online advertising and marketing products to initiate a buzz within specific districts